hi welcome back to The Wheel of Life
series retreat online machine and today
we're gonna do for session six I'm sorry
we're gonna do a meditation hi slam dunk
humble idiotic a top 100 online
non-toxic akitaka melaku cut Medina see
and during this online retreat we're
discussing three kinds or actually four
kinds of meditation you can do to warm
up for your real meditation dance Lamar
upon la única tottenham mom awesome
button this meditation misunder guna
cannot Manasa
and of course we did there seven
preparation steps already - koukin - de
la cara open now today we're gonna do
what's called the eight technique
meditations and our unique atacama
cookin up in is somewhat made it a seal
upon technique and these meditations
help you improve your meditation
technique that made it a cinnamon bun -
man in cap gun technic minotaur see
under they're not actually meditations
themselves but it does miss women are
yeah it's like we are just building a
stronger microscope but we're not
looking at anything with the microscope
subong means cross-table be quite a
Paquita determine sorry I pop under the
microscope it - so these meditations are
kind of exciting new midi tasini
intelligently sound when you're not done
and kind of sexy sexy but please
they are not real meditation nothing but
I kinda do comedy touchy so song good
yeah you're just sharpening the knife
you're not cutting the fruit yet
underhand among us off these sound them
up Tom Walker cutting the food is real
meditation is sharpening the knife is
just improving your concentration
these softening cut can concentran see
under if you always say it a different
way Uganda in Bogota continent sorry I'm
gonna be you can say these eight
technique meditations help you reach
shamaton under the panna cotta pen
Mohammed ethos implement technically
Nima bun to undermine Champa Champa and
shemitah' means literally it means
peaceful peacefulness
then shemitah' party shutter on fear and
the lock at the noggin but it means the
kind of perfect focus you're going to
have to develop if you want to see
emptiness later the people are P so much
I'm focus important under arc on her
skunk and chica and I mean million
Turkish oven on Dean
so personally in my daily meditation
sauna provided a limited class in sorry
hari I mix up different preliminaries so
I'm a jumper grappa Bob rapid responding
better some days I feel like doing the
seven kilometers because I'd like to
start with my teacher and I don't say
eyebrows I didn't lock you can teach it
I don't know sorry I need mobile I
demand guru saya and that's a very
powerful Karma for starting your
meditation don't need total up our minds
a lot of ammonium it it does the under
but sometimes before meditation topic
and evidence of low militancy I like to
use this 8 technique meditation so you
can make it doesn't love on technique
and sometimes I wanna call them getting
quiet meditations pattern I don't say
yeah sooo coming in would be immediate
assignment editor and the goal of this 8
is to get quieter and quieter and
quieter than to generate lopunny need
Allah I don't open today let me turn a
little bit another Lapita and then you
shift to the real meditation under ali
khamenei toss is enough so in session 6
today he says seeing mom hurry me
we're just gonna practice this 8 getting
quieter technique meditations get the
Heineken allotted love on meditation
technique major deal of autonomy and
then in tomorrow's segment seven chakras
in eg I'll show you how to use those
eight to get into your meditation and
then do a real meditation you can do not
come till upon it so Candela maybe it
does under SSO guna the picture that we
use for this 8 is a picture of the sky
and the sea - clapping in ear the lumber
along it and louder and you'll
understand that more as we go through
this meditation huh millimeter Sunita
seen these are traditionally divided
into two sets of 4 and 4 any sort of
traditional to begin me to do a certain
pattern but
and nickname for them in Tibetan
Buddhism is some suck some soup then I'm
a Pongal America due to this motivated a
Lhasa Apso son is a short for something
some adolescent cotton there is
something and something like Keanu in
Sanskrit
sometimes pas de las casas Carta and the
word
Jan 14 cups from that then Cap'n's an
opposed end result Erica PI 2 so the
first so actually all meditations are
Indiana the recent Nana some amadito
said a la pierna but the first four are
together traditionally they are called
something she the for meditation levels
the beam pattern pertama star a
tradition on all this about sometimes
she but pink upon Marita see and as you
know if you studied the lion stance and
support the Undertown chica blood your
Italian singer these these are divided
into cause meditations and result
meditations eatery buggy menjadi Morita
sister Buckland meditation hustle cause
meditation means Matassa suburb property
if you do this for some tents or
journalists over and over in this life
chicken table koukin but sometime you
need auto da naboo like a little appear
to be me many many many times
starring Kali when you die could he come
up T you could be born into what we call
the form realm under Bashar dealer can't
cut apart and get us of the dunya Ruben
form is also a nickname Ben took
analodjica nemanja and it means the
realm of beings who look like
superheroes into bra tease dunya motoki
eternally had supported beloved super
so in that realm everybody looks like
Iron Man or Thor or Wonder Woman jdd
denier to Samarra totally had support
the Iron Man at all saw that I wonder
would they have very very beautiful
forms become a milky but took some had
such an ending that disturb would maybe
the Sydney Opera but then we go to the
second set of four now look at the
masuka's butts that can do up so the
whole eight are called Sam sook goodies
a little glop buddies of the Sun so the
Sun means is something four kinds of
meditation to reach the form rebirth of
for Thor and Iron Man some one of these
some can imagine is Vanitas it opens up
I do never been talked to Herod cabal
eat or an Iron Men and to call it
I can set sook is very confusing now
that minion boots that can do a sook
summon being woken because silk means
physical form turner sook but our people
can physic but really those realms are
so may not be some nara dunya toward
elastic men form lesson we meet up again
you are born without any girls physical
body than underlie here bumper to be
physical sword asana if you do this
formula tests you can you can see
whether you become four or whether you
become a person who is just the brain
and nobody
ibaka and abilities for atomically
orange even yesterday urinary dinner
you're you are still in sensor under my
CD sansara and there's a lot of
suffering everybody's under so we don't
do these meditations to reach those two
realms and I'm like okay maybe I seen
him on top I could what do we use these
meditations to get quieter and quieter
and quieter so we can do a higher
military the top uh committee toss in a
little bit another Lebanon singer kita
bersama cook a mediator Celebi thingy so
when you say we're trying to reach
shemitahs critic endemic apartment key
president opens up like Shamu it doesn't
mean peace in the sense of Nirvana into
did a branded Amidala Marty Nirvana
it means peace in the sense of perfect
concentration developing debate on a
party concentration some porno and
perfect quiet done because I know at
some point so let's start gotta get the
male take your meditation position I'm
bill process you may be passing under
make sure you come to learn don't start
your meditation entire a really
comfortable house take another Sonya Mon
Cala mobile America see supplement
governor and argument
stomach is a little bit lower abdomen is
a little bit pushed in to begin again
but I was thinking Doraemon so the
perfect way to do that
turn on some porno taco Canyon when you
exhale the gundermen caboose cannabis
then push a little extra air but also
they get lippy you gotta include one and
that will also prevent problems with too
much prana build-up to do Kappa Gamma
solid and enter Lando by the : Brad all
this back buddha park a block um just a
little water
the hands come back on the legs a little
bit longer the parks a big idiot Aloha
faces come watch afternoon many of us
when we concentrate we scowl or
forgotten or inserted our city to grow
so try to concentrate without scaling I
I like to play music did he trouble a
poor concentration but I also compromise
music when I play sitar for example I
scour the gob remind sit-ups but the top
laisse tomber
because I'm concentrating abracadabra
see so during meditation especially this
aid that Islam Americas you to
automatically open in II try to
concentrate the don't scour come on
content receipt up Internet number the
face is very pleasant one giant summits
on no relaxed Sun by little smile
suddenly kids a new one now usually we
start a meditation by watching our
breath for about ten breaths
yes inevitable American citizen baba
Baba cannabis kita Lamas guitar super
luminous but is traditional especially
in the lion's den some people try to
show not Obama Delhomme Darian Cigna
till start this meditation in a
completely different way namu Amida pass
you need even support our young samus
caliber business so before you start the
aid to discipline under moonlight
lopunny me we're going to listen to any
subtle sounds in this room atacama
Americans wore a hollow sphere on Nene
it might be the sound a few cars outside
monkey in for a proper mo building water
it might be the sound of some family
members in your apartment looking for a
pop up on what a quantity apartment
under the sound of a refrigerator is
very difficult in most houses swara
focus on sonic boom boom do cabanaconde
rumba
in this room right now you know on eNOS
Karam at the cedilha College of
International Management
the compass FC I am and the headquarters
of a CI that contact us at NCI we have
air conditioning going right now and the
ASEAN celebrity lenska so whatever sound
you have available in your place the
Apapa union under military combat under
please put your mind on that some
silicon taru pick it up and apparatus
all right I enjoy the image of putting
my head on a pillow so I am adding a
button when I'm some of them on the back
at the palace idea bomb when I put my
head on my pillow at night I so enjoy
that moment because I am in a Buttkicker
couple ideas but the malamar I saw a
sonic mati sati do
and the head goes down to the pillow
Paulo children come on doll and it stays
there not the company's honor you don't
raise your head put it back raise your
head pretty bad I raise your head but
you don't do that I don't think I'm
gonna cut couple omelet up at the Kamali
monitor Kabbalah Kabbalah Karunya sound
meditation before you do the ape
technically annotation food maybe fancy
swallow some empty table who can maybe
toss it
clapping technique please relax your
mind on that sound in your room like you
are putting your hand on a pillow and
leave it there Hartman on up and begin
Amanda but there's already combo super
be uncomfortable and it was pumped out
that money got Sonia dishonor
here we go wanna give my Stanley and I
will put her mind on the air
conditioning Stanley done sire
Padmanabha we cannot come upon her ass
see again firstly I'd like to time the
parts of my meditation soliloquy sorry
buddy saya suka monkey talk about gender
America is a song governor I might do
ten prayers on each part or or 20 I am
spoon up as for the Muslims in
Malibu Lou people ask me isn't that a
distraction when you think about your
breath when you're supposed to think
about the early missionary
oh no poor Panda you can try to come
home to the Condor predicament on AAPIs
but the house house of a bigger
paparazzi but if you practice meditation
everyday
propaganda but not immediate assist fre
the ten breaths becomes natural to you
support representative Allah will put
you under and it won't be a discharge I
need to determine the return code area
or camera guitar boy
you
try to keep your mind on the sound so
Balaam on joka begin and end up at a
swap
you
now we're going to go into the first of
the eight technique meditations the
current apartment market for Tom Adair
emeritus Islam and evening
and please put your mind on your
heartbeat Dunmurry manaro página 10 de
nada for me it feels like I'm in my head
and I'm kind of feeling my heart beat in
my chest
miss Eyre a scientist I develop Kabbalah
and Resaca Jean tobert indeed a desire
and I'm not inside the heart I'm just
observing the trans I didn't brag a
little on junto animal Amontillado
if you meditate a lot and if you have a
quiet place to meditate you can follow
your heart be pulse the pulse in your
ears you can do by the 4-minute acid
Angela mom illegitimate Antonin Oh Devon
irritants and Arabic manicotti the
captain - under na dhih dhih cling under
so here we go did you see the Kitab
online relax but now don't rush just
have fun
- come on now please remember to push
the birth dad at the excel our opinion
and of onderon Apostolos
at the end of the exhale I can undo son
until your lower abdomen tightens very
slightly some very poor power so the
kids Cali all throughout this meditation
someone else but the minute I see okay
let's let's focus on our heartbeat and
try not to think of other things
okay mari focus button at the top John
Doe done it up on me Caroline the these
eight meditations are described as
dropping the last level and moving up to
the next level and it does it la
política merkins about him La Paz
contain a tracker on her are tapping
contribute
each lovers more quiet than the last
lover higher higher quiet some depth in
coupla people under a big attraction let
me think
Gila beaten so you almost consciously
say I'm I'm gonna I'm gonna stop
listening to the air-conditioner and I'm
gonna move up to a quieter heart deep
did he end up your son us other my
parents I abandoned him another can I
say
plus I haven't peed at a dump at the
dock gentlemen Lily Tomlin
so try to stay on the heart being and
try not to listen to the air-conditioner
anymore
delete Abelardo cut up and a deduction
don't admit about the peanut menorquin
are Ceylon tea you should feel like
you're getting quieter and quieter and I
was Ross's Papa Mia and I'm a dirty
smack in the mountain let me
you
they were going to cook go even more
quiet come on get back on Massimo Canale
pendant lucky the second of the a
technique meditations
I'm gonna do a dairymaid he doesn't
clump up Ahmed let's go inside our heart
market AMA super gallant and Anita they
were still T listening to the heart Dave
Yamazaki New York undertook Tonto
but it will feel like the walls of our
little meditation room are beating
because we're inside the heart
Dunley top in Terezin spotted in being
wrong it has officially picked up at the
top carpentry cover lady Dellinger
[Music]
now the inside of the heart is kind of
wet and gooey
starbuck intelligent Osama suckling
but for this meditation opt to see me
you have to imagine that inside the
heart is a lovely elegant meditation
room under some abaya condom on general
aptitude interferometer tossing an
elegant
sunlight is coming through the windows
not even a booster dela you have a very
comfortable meditation scene under
public equals in meditation sermon it's
super quiet but the walls around you the
heart walls are beating so pertinent
ability leading this guitar under the
gentle
so now drop down from your head
did he Scotland to America pal under and
enter your heart that was so o'clock I'd
end up dead on under and let's stay in
that more quiet place that Mariquita
tingle it up a little bit but now with
the hard dealing around this in the
reduction Tony's in Turkey
you
now we'll go to the third technique
meditation the third part of the form
real meditation
Sagarika dr. muscle committee doesn't
technically la pagina together imitate
insignia bourbon and imagine there's a
meditation room at the center of your
meditation but by in Canada or America
Sidi Bouzid wrong may be passing under I
like to think of it like a very
expensive apartment on the top of a of a
tall apartment building
let's I set up the prickers but the
apartment in salad model the hospital
about a million pinky and all the
windows are glass and some mozzarella
terracotta
and there's a room at the center of the
apartment that I've done wrong and even
some apartment and I go into that and
say I'm also gonna want me to and I
close the door
there's still some sunlight coming in
Los Zetas inaudible Pahari on muscle and
it's still a beautiful elegant room with
good air and the woman must endure
elegant in the buidling bite
but the heart beating in the walls
Abhijit or deducted ending now it sounds
very far away very faint Naropa banner
saga Johnson at Zama okay here we go
okay America Tom also to the meditation
room at the center of the heart the
wrong militancy departed
even more quiet most of the people
you
now I'd like you to imagine a small
table I assign the current site
inaudible by a thumbs up America Chile
CC under inside this inner room of the
heart develop wrong and a gallon jug
boom and sitting on that table is a
small part of sugar
the itas major supporter Tilbury
singular white sugar gulapa tea and you
lift off the lid of the sugar pop pop
pop kula and with the third finger of
your left hand then demand dirty money
spanking under you just touched the
sugar slightly women talk cool I know
something
and you lift a finger pathetically water
and there's a few grains of sugar on the
tip of your Dada Papa booty goolah 'du
ginger anger focus on one of those
grains of sugar focus butter sauce Abu
Bakr Coola and then think to yourself
then go a particular scenario I would
like to be inside that sugar crystal
Messiah in brother did Alan crystal gula
it's super Cryer in a Superman it's also
super anonymous who's gonna find you in
the whole room inside a sugar crystal to
go super unknown in Japan a commentary
on daddy's little rebellion crystal Kuna
in the whole world and the whole
universe it's a tiny tiny tiny tiny
little place this little dunya be smooth
all up someone start at the potato two
potato sandwiches Akane if I go inside
there I'll be super quiet because I am
also develops on Sayaka
no one would ever find me doing here
Akhenaten McEntire his son so imagine
you're opening a door into the crest
into the sugar crystal kopaka Pinto
Khurana crystal Cola
and you kind of squeeze your mind
through the little door but I was about
to begin to kind of begin an indelible
ami bit about you then you're very
surprised inside it it's a third
meditation room very kind of large and
very comfortable put it on a puppet it
alumni they're wrong but it doesn't
Attica Aqaba something someone
light is coming in through the edges of
the crystal
I am also allowing cccc's crystal and
you sit down and meditate inside there
but not to do poor American citizen if
someone came into your main meditation
room at this moment you know in your
house Chickasaw sort of muscle car obey
because you and aperitivo
how could they ever bother you you are
in a single like you're it's like you're
in a single atom in a huge room under
dull super teeny operati develops are to
Adam don't go the talents of gone wrong
and bizarre
so let's go inside did America Tomaso
and meditate very very quiet inside no
more heart didn't are done per minute
and see so that's not indeed illuminated
at the top gentles almost golly
you
now let's take a challenge Skarmory get
the horribly supported on the fifth of
the eighth technique meditations we
began column adore American syllabi
magnet which is the first of the
formless realm meditations the other lab
again Papa Madurai maybe toss it in your
turn purple do we take a challenge
katomina Beelzebub and diamond can you
fit the whole Pacific Ocean insider that
sugar crystal vodka and governments to
consider us a mudra Pacific Adela
Bristol moonlight do so now you're you
become the Pacific Ocean that is kind of
uncommon that is above the Pacific
you're a thousands of miles wide and
high bar under the rim one meal you're a
few miles deep under to come but grab a
meal dalam you cover a good tired of the
whole world could be spoken bizarre
there is little duniya the Pacific Ocean
Pacific means peaceful than somewhat
representing the Pacific grant be doubly
so you're this Steve peaceful blue ocean
the under Parata is somewhat ribeirão
and galloped under mine
totally silent
you
let's go even bigger bra broader
Mariquita Mandela people start on the
bill was let's add the whole blue sky to
the blue water mari kita amber conce
ljubljana Piro Piro Piro this is the
picture we used for this meditation in
an elaborate Kotaku Nakano top medical
scene I am the entire play sky so I add
a la salut
Peru and I am the entire blue Pacific
oceans I add a la Samudra Pacific beer
I stretch from the bottom of the ocean
to the top of this guy I am but and
arrogant element Samudra Samba capital
Ani
totally peaceful when I Bernard am I
totally calm
when I've done
you
what could be more quiet than none open
be celibate a nunnery
what if I just turned my whole mind off
like a light like a magnetic rasayana
mamata cuts a little prick Arabs I
assume that it's a higher
it's actually technically it's not
possible so nurse are not technically to
do the monkey but let's pretend happy
Monica double cool I'm gonna turn my
mind off like a life so I've got my
money can't begin in science and this
will be more quiet than anything before
Nene up and abhijanati bundy continents
alumna like completely unconscious
support the man opened our data actor
the duck sucker watch your mind you can
begin an under keep it super quiet no
talking in the mind at all the top super
commentator burpees are indelible
karin-sama skully
if a thought comes through you gotta be
get a new data if some random image
comes to Jakarta proper governmental if
some interruption from the outside comes
into the mine
Ricardo propaganda enormous copy Kiran
go through it I'm beauty and block it
doesn't walk in here
tell her to shut up put it up push it
out of the mind very beginner okay here
we go
you
we're going to go to meditation level if
apparently pop all I militancy think
upon the highest level of the formless
realm meditations which lead you to the
formless room if you do them alone in
this life pick a particular American
city metadata token mobile and hakuna
mutata condom on coke on a syringe a
little girl a panini
now I'm also going to shut up the part
of my mind which is watching my mind to
see if my mind is thinking about
anything
spelling sign took up a balloon Jesus
about yet that it became Ryan Republican
because I only got a pocke
a day on Saddam's I think you're gonna
be Kira
now if random thoughts or ideas come to
my mind
come on take a peek at an utter kappa
edewin suck another pigeon in fire no
one will be there to hear them it up
akhenaten women or Kutner which is a
deeper quiet place now I talked about a
little bit but golem dun dun dun
nobody even watching did a card I am
melihat near this Joe Murray get hurt Oh
you
now let's dedicate the meditation car
America today classic American CLE is a
technique meditations may be totsied
lapin technique just with the Virginia
higher than this all the people in the
world would find this kind of peace and
crying I never can have up and develop
at the under bono some more on the dunya
economy mechanical dominance of the
inning
you
slowly open your eyes grandma Bucca
matanga take a stretch black Cobra gonna
see you tomorrow in the next station
some pie cutter bombay stock decisive
break up